Adventure beyond Pixie Hollow
Tinker Bell and the Lost Treasure is a animation,
family, adventure film directed by Klay Hall.
A blue harvest moon will rise, allowing the fairies to use a precious moonstone
to restore the Pixie Dust Tree, the source of all their magic.
But when Tinker Bell accidentally puts all of Pixie Hollow in jeopardy, she must
venture out across the sea on a secret quest to set things right.
Tinker Bell (voice), played by Mae Whitman.
Terence (voice), played by Jesse McCartney.
Fairy Mary (voice), played by Jane Horrocks.
Silvermist (voice), played by Lucy Liu.
Iridessa (voice), played by Raven-Symoné.
Rosetta (voice), played by Kristin Chenoweth.
Tinker Bell and the Lost Treasure is a 2009 American animated fantasy adventure film
directed by Klay Hall and the second installment in the Disney Fairies franchise.
Produced by Disneytoon Studios, it was animated by Prana Studios, and
revolves around Tinker Bell, a fairy character created by J.
Barrie in his 1904 play Peter Pan, or The Boy Who Wouldn't Grow Up, and featured
in subsequent adaptations, especially in Disney's animated works.
It was released on Blu-ray and DVD by Walt Disney Studios
Home Entertainment on October 27, 2009.
The film was followed by more direct-to-video films: Tinker Bell and the Great Fairy Rescue, Secret
of the Wings, The Pirate Fairy and Tinker Bell and the Legend of the NeverBeast.
The film explores themes of friendship, based on children's book, anger issues.